The sky wakes up when the sun goes down.
A million electric eyes over the town.
Turn the key and feel the hum in the floor. We're
leaving the shadows right outside the door.
Catch the neon pulse riding on the wire.
Racing through the streets. Blowing like a
fire. No looking back. We're out of frame.
Running on the spark. Wild and untamed. Catch
the neon pulse tonight.
The End
The dashboard is glowing, a steady bright
green.
The fastest escape that this city has seen. The
rhythm is beating
right under our feet. A steady transmission.
Out on the street Catch the neon pulse Riding on
the wire Racing through the streets Glowing
like a fire No looking back We're out of the frame
Burning on the spark Wild and untamed Catch the
neon pulse tonight
Hey.
Through the tunnel of lights, blinding and fast
Everything broken is left in the past
Hold on to the wheel, steady and sure
We're chasing a frequency, perfect and pure
Catch
the neon pulse Riding on the wire Racing through
the streets Glowing like a fire No looking back
We're out of the frame Running on the spark Wild
and untamed Catch the neon pulse tonight
Wild and untamed
Catch the pulse tonight